{
    "subject": "resource/In_the_Name_of_the_Father_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/budget",
    "object": "1.3E7",
    "human_readable": "The budget of the film 'In the Name of the Father' is 1.3 million.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9268317818641663,
            "question": "What was the budget for the film 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290437817573547,
            "question": "Was 'In the Name of the Father' a low-budget film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122849822044373,
            "question": "What are some typical budget ranges for films with historical themes like 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6802907586097717,
            "question": "Could the budget of 'In the Name of the Father' be considered significant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6533674597740173,
            "question": "What factors might have influenced the budget of 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6503350734710693,
            "question": "What could have been achieved with an increased budget for 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6483532786369324,
            "question": "How does the budget of 'In the Name of the Father' compare to other films of a similar genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6352638006210327,
            "question": "Could the budget have impacted the overall success of 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6042218804359436,
            "question": "Do you think the budget of 'In the Name of the Father' was a good investment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5052441954612732,
            "question": "How much money was invested in making 'In the Name of the Father'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The budget of the film 'In the Name of the Father' is 1.3 million.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6752_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you think the budget of 'In the Name of the Father' was a good investment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6752_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could the budget have impacted the overall success of 'In the Name of the Father'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6752_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the budget of 'In the Name of the Father' compare to other films of a similar genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6752_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6752_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that \"In the Name of the Father\" was based on a true story and does not give any information about its budget.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information provided does not mention any details about the budget for the film \"In the Name of the Father.\" It only mentions that a producer was instructed to work with a very low budget, but no specific amount is given. Therefore, the statement that the budget of the film 'In the Name of the Father' is 1.3 million is not supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information about the budget of \"In the Name of the Father\" isn't mentioned in the provided context.  It discusses the Conlons' situation, the film's acclaim, and its plot points but lacks any financial details related to its production.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the budget of \"The Troops of Saint-Tropez\" was 1.3 million francs (less than \u20ac200,000), not \"In the Name of the Father\".",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}